infotech-enterprises.com 2019-06-13

# Privacy Policy - Cyient

The privacy and security of your personal data is of the utmost importance to Cyient Ltd. and all of its operating companies globally (‘Cyient’) and we invest heavily into measures that help protect your data protection rights. This policy describes how and why we collect, store, process and manage the personal data we hold from our data subjects. The term ‘Personal Data’ refers to any information relating to an identifiable individual or his or her personal identity. This policy outlines how your data will be processed lawfully, fairly and in a transparent manner. Cyient does not sell or rent your personal data to third parties for marketing purposes whatsoever. We will ensure that the personal data we process is accurate, adequate, relevant and not excessive, given the purpose for which it was obtained. We will not process personal data obtained for one purpose for any unconnected purpose unless the person has agreed to this or would otherwise reasonably expect this. Cyient collects your personal data in order to manage your relationship with us. We also collect your data so that we can send you marketing information regarding our products, promotions, and services for which you have provided your consent for receiving the communication.

The Office for Information Security who is responsible for ensuring that personal data is managed responsibly throughout the company. You can contact the Office for Information Security using the details listed at the end of this document.

You have the right to see the data we hold on you, rectify that data and also for requesting us to delete that data at any time.

1\. Introduction

1.1 Cyient is defined as the data controller with regard to all of the information contained in this document.

1.2 This Privacy Policy sets out the way in which Cyient, collects and processes Personal Information of our data subjects. Cyient is registered for the purposes of data protection with the Information Commissioner’s Office in the UK. (Registration Reference No. ZA381727). 

1.3 By using our services and/or registering your consent, you acknowledge that you have read, and agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy in relation to processing under legitimate interests.

2\. The information we collect

2.1 As part of maintaining your relationship with us, we collect your Personal Information. “Personal Information” means any information from which you, as a ‘data subject’, can be personally identified, including for example your name, email address, home address, telephone number, or date of birth.

2.2 We collect your Personal Information when you register your interest; for example through the use of online forms and when you email us your details. We also collect information about the transactions you undertake with us. 

2.3 In addition, we may collect Personal Information through surveys which we undertake. Such surveys are voluntary and are anonymous where possible.

3\. Your rights as a ‘data subject’

3.1 Under data protection law you retain the following rights over your personal data outlined in paragraph 3.2.

3.2  
The right to access the data we hold about you  
The right to rectification of any data that is inaccurate or incomplete.  
The right to erasure of your data (also known as ‘the right to be forgotten’)  
The right to restrict processing of your data   
The right to data portability  
The right to object to the processing of your data  
Rights in relation to automated decision making and profiling. 

3.3 If you exercise your right to be forgotten, this would result in a termination of your relationship with Cyient. 

4\. Our basis for processing personal data

4.1 For the purpose of managing our business, it is important for us to maintain your personal information.

4.2 It is a requirement of our terms and conditions that any person who wishes to attend or partake in the services offered by us should provide the necessary personal information. 

4.3 Information collected and processed for the purposes of your engagement with us is done so on the basis of a legitimate interest. The justification for this is outlined in 4.1 above.

4.4 In order to keep you up to date with our news and promotional events we create and send regular marketing information via direct marketing, SMS, email, and other digital channels. In order to send you this information, we will ensure that we have your consent. This is usually obtained at the point of registration.

4.5 This consent can be withdrawn at any time by contacting the Office for Information Security using the details below. 

5\. How we use your Personal Information

5.1 Your Personal Information is processed by us to provide you with the products and services relating to our business. In particular, we collect your Personal Information in order to enable us to:

  * Set-up, administer and manage your relationship, associated accounts and records; 
  * Receive and respond to your communications and requests;
  * Notify you about promotional offers and general marketing;
  * Ensure that we are able to fulfil our regulatory obligations regarding your account, including by verifying the accuracy of any information you give us;
  * Comply with our obligations under applicable laws;
  * Investigate, and assist with the investigation of, suspected unlawful, fraudulent or other improper activity connected with the services (including, where appropriate, dealing with requests from regulatory bodies for the sharing of information);
  * Carry out market research and marketing campaigns;
  * Consider you for potential job openings within our organisation;
  * In the event that we sell or buy any business, assets or shares in part or whole we may disclose your personal details to such relevant third parties involved.

6\. Disclosure of your Personal Information

6.1 We may disclose your Personal Information to any of the following recipients:

  * Any company within the Cyient Group (including to its employees and sub-contractors) which assists us in providing the services or which otherwise has a need to know such information.
  * Any contractors or other advisers auditing any of our business processes or who have the need to access such information for the purpose of advising us.
  * Any data processor which enable us to manage systems or processes as part of any service or promotion offered to you. However, we will take reasonable steps to ensure that these data processors are compliant with GDPR requirements.
  * Any law enforcement or regulatory body which may have any reasonable requirement to access your Personal Information.
  * In the event that we sell or buy any business, assets or shares in part or whole we may disclose your personal details to such relevant third parties involved.

7\. Marketing Preferences

7.1 We will not send you unsolicited information regarding any third party’s products or services.

7.2 When submitting your information through the Cyient website, you will have the opportunity to choose whether or not to receive information on our offers and promotions. This consent is subject to the data retention periods defined within this policy.

7.3 Existing data subjects who registered prior to 25 May 2018 - if you have not opted out of receiving communications from us, we will assume legitimate business purpose in sending marketing communication whilst including the option to opt out every time such communications are sent out to you. The product, service or ideals we are marketing to you are the same or similar to those that you originally consented to receive marketing at the time of enrolment, and therefore it is reasonable for you to receive marketing material from us. 

7.4 We will send you promotional marketing information and updates until such time that you inform us that you do not wish to continue to receive them or do not refresh your consent upon our request at the end of 5 years from the date of your consent. You may update your marketing preferences at any time by contacting your business point of contact within Cyient or through the [request for services/contact form](https://go.cyient.com/request-for-services) on our website. 

8\. Accessing and Updating your Personal Information 

8.1 You may update your Personal Information at any time by contacting the Office for Information Security using the details below.

8.2 You may obtain a copy of your Personal Information held by us by contacting via the contact information provided at the end of this document. We require up to one month in order to respond to such requests.

8.3 Requests for access to your personal data are free of charge.

9\. How long do we keep your data for?

9.1 We retain your data for no longer than is necessary. This length of time is different for each type of personal data that we hold. These retention periods are subject to change only where deemed necessary by the Office for Information Security where there is a defined vital interest under data protection law.

9.2 Data retention periods:

Data subject information | Data retained for 5 years after data subjects’ most recent visit.  
---|---  
Marketing Preferences | Data retained for 5 years from consent being given.  
Information required by legislation  | Data retained for 10 years after data subjects’ most recent visit.  
  
10\. Advertising and use of cookies

10.1 We may collect anonymous information about your use of the Cyient.com website using “cookies”, pixel tags and similar functionality. We use cookies for the operation of the website. We also use cookies for our own analytical purposes so that we can improve our customers’ experience. Once you navigate away from our website, please be aware that our privacy policy will be superseded by the provisions of the host website. Digital advertisements on third-party platforms are served to you based on your profile and privacy settings with the advertising platform and are governed by their policy.

10.2 If you object to cookies or want to delete any cookies that are already stored on your computer, you should follow the instructions for deleting existing cookies and disabling future cookies on your web browser or equivalent software. Further information is available at [www.aboutcookies.org](http://www.aboutcookies.org/).

10.3 As part of the website’s operation, and for our own statistical analysis of site traffic, our website automatically logs internet IP addresses. 

11\. Security

11.1 We use a number of methods to ensure that all customer information remains confidential. We have developed a comprehensive policy for data protection management which is reviewed and updated as necessary.

12\. Complaints

Cyient takes the personal data we hold very seriously and is happy to receive any queries or concerns you may have. If you believe that we have not adhered to this policy or that your data has been handled in a way which you feel is not in accordance with your wishes then you may complain to the Office for Information Security using the contact details below.

Alternatively you may contact the Information Commissioners Officer (ICO) directly who is the body responsible for managing data protection compliance in the UK. 

You can contact the ICO at the following address:

Information Commissioner's Office  
Wycliffe House  
Water Lane

Wimslow  
Cheshire  
SK9 5AF  
casework@ico.org.uk  
0303 123 1113

13\. Contact information

Please contact us via the [contact form](https://go.cyient.com/compliance) on our website or in writing at;

Compliance Manager  
The Space Holborn  
235 High Holborn  
London, WC1V 7LE  
UK
